<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>MGKenins RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.mgk.ac</link>
    <description>The official RSS Feed for https://www.mgk.ac</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:01:55 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Status update, February 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.mgk.ac/posts/2023-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;status-update-february-2023&quot;&gt;Status update, February 2023&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;date&quot;&gt;2023-03-04&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, welcome to my website. 
This is probably your first time seeing it, but it just went through a
major makeover. I’ve archived &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20221223055937/https://adast.xyz/&quot;&gt;the old
design&lt;/a&gt; if
you want to check it out.
The new design is &lt;em&gt;blazingly fast&lt;/em&gt;, light as a feather, and anyone can navigate
it.
This redesign was heavily inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://btxx.org&quot;&gt;btxx.org&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;https://drewdevault.com&quot;&gt;drewdevault.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find my contact details and important links on the homepage.
There are links to more information about myself and this website, projects I’m
working on, and my RSS feed at the top.
I’ve included my PGP key if you wish to send me mail privately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CompSci department at my uni hosts an annual LAN party with tournaments
in the usual titles (csgo, lol, trackmania, etc). It would be amazing to get &lt;a href=&quot;https://arena.adast.dk&quot;&gt;arena&lt;/a&gt; to a playable,
fun state, and have a LAN tournament to really put it to the test.
I want to start working on my game again, and I want to it to be playable in
time for the LAN party.
I have about 5 weeks to make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a few technical blog posts planned, but I’ll also just be posting
about anything I that interests me.
I think I’ll start doing monthly status updates (like this post), much like
the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sourcehut.org/consultancy/#our-engineers&quot;&gt;engineers at
sourcehut.org&lt;/a&gt;.
I’d also like to start posting (weekly) development logs for arena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I have a lot more services I need to start hosting before I really
call this &lt;em&gt;my platform&lt;/em&gt;. You can see the list of publicly available
services by clicking the link at the top of the page. For now, I’m
prioritising hosting the services that I use regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book club:&lt;/strong&gt; I’m reading A Voyage for Madmen by Peter Nichols.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2023-03-04T12:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2025-11-13T13:01:55+01:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>